http://www.wags411.org/sites/wags/privacy-policy

Menu
HomeGame SchedulesWAGS Information About UsCode of ConductBoard of DirectorsLeague By-LawsCalendarFrom the CommishDownloadsLocationsDivision DetailsConcessions ProceduresEquipmentFAQsRefund PolicyWAGS WearPast Seasons 2009 Season 20092009-Opening Day2009-A/S2009-HR2010 Season 20102010 Opening Day2010 HR2010 A/S2011201220132014 Home Run Club 20142015 Home Run Club 2015Final Standings 20152016 TeeBall Rosters 20166U Rosters 20168U Rosters 201610U Rosters 201612U Rosters 2016Home Run Club 20162017 TeeBall Rosters 20176U Rosters 20178U Rosters 2017 10U Rosters 201712U Rosters 201714U Roster 2017Home Run Club 2017Playoff Brackets2018 Season 6U Rosters 20188U Rosters 201810U Rosters 201812U Rosters 201814U Select Roster 2018TeeBall Rosters 2018Home Run Club 20182019 Season Home Run Club 2019Fundraising Events WAGS Movie NightBirdies & Bases FundraiserPrograms CurrentUpcomingPlayer Development ClinicsPreseason TrainingOther ClinicsContact UsCOVID-19 USA Softball GuidancePublic Health Information
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our
newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as
appropriate you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card
information. However, you may visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: * To personalize your experience
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
* To improve our website
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the
information and feedback we receive from you.* To improve customer service
Your information helps
us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.* To process
transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred,
or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever without your consent, other than for the express purpose of
delivering the purchased product or service requested.* To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates
pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service
information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we
include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of
your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket
Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those
authorized with special access rights to such systems and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will
not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies? Yes. Cookies are small
files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you
allow). This enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember
certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or
otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties
agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is
appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or
safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing,
advertising, or other uses.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with
the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act) and we do not collect any information from anyone
under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years of age
or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only
to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your
Consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our
Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this
page.
WAGS Information
About UsCalendarDivision DetailsFAQsField LocationsEquipmentConcessions ProceduresBoard of DirectorsCode of ConductLessons/PartnersWAGS AlumniWAGS Through The YearsWAGS Wear
Fundraising
Fundraising Dinner
All Stars
General Info
Coach's Corner
Manager InformationManager ApplicationManager's HandbookConcussion ProtocolSkills & DrillsSoftball CheersField Set-Up
WAGS Links
USA Softball SoCalUSA SoftballACE Coach EducationResponsible SportsSoftball Excellence
